{
    "id": "5574c9d16c68483799c6149723e4f065",
    "title": "Phrasal prepositions exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7daad3ef116e4f41962f80150ce3ec45",
            "title": "Phrasal Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………….. his hard work, he failed the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "By means of",
                        "In spite of",
                        "Because of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… doctors, smoking can cause cancer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In accordance with",
                        "According to",
                        "On behalf of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am standing here ………………… my colleagues.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "instead of",
                        "by means of",
                        "on behalf of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The trains arrived late ……………….. heavy rains.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in spite of",
                        "on behalf of",
                        "because of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I stayed in bed all day ……………… going to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in addition to",
                        "in spite of",
                        "instead of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Thoughts are conveyed ………………… words.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on account of",
                        "by means of",
                        "by virtue of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Gandhi gave up his legal practice ………………… his country.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by virtue of",
                        "for the sake of",
                        "on behalf of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. his own family, he has to support his brother’s.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "In addition to",
                        "Instead of",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a school …………………. my house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "front of",
                        "in front of",
                        "in front"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would like to have lemon juice ………………… coffee.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "instead",
                        "instead of",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}